https://www.ablelabel.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Effective: January 1, 2018Able Label is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to our website and will not sell any non-public personal information to third parties that resell the information or send out unsolicited bulk or commercial emails (Spam). Able Label will only share your information with our trusted Partners to fulfill your orders and carry out our business, or as required by law.Types of Information Cookies. A Cookie is a randomly generated unique number placed on your computer. It allows us to identify your computer without requiring disclosure of any Non-Public Personal Information. Cookies make it possible to both store and retrieve information through your internet browser, such as items placed in a shopping cart. A Cookie itself cannot read information off a hard drive or read Cookie files from other sites.General Information is information that does not reveal your identity. General Information may include, without limitation: generic business type; SIC code; information derived from publicly available databases (such as Dun and Bradstreet); user behavior on our Web site; and aggregated generic information. Non-Public Personal Information is any non-public information you provide to us or our Partners that is proprietary, or identifies, or can be used to identify, contact, or locate you or someone at your business. Non-Public Personal Information may include, without limitation: name; address; phone number; e-mail address; credit card number; account information; spending patterns; and individual tastes and preferences. Partners are individuals or entities we engage to help us carry out our mission. What Information We CollectAble Label collects general information and non-public personal information.How We Collect Our InformationAble Label collects our general information through the use of cookies and server-based tracking systems to view the usage of the website.Non-public personal information is collected through registration or contact forms on this site and will never be used for any purpose other than internal use or by our partners unless the registrant chooses to be added to mailing lists (the registrant makes this choice on the Registration form). Privacy Policy ChangesAny changes to this privacy policy will be posted here unless otherwise noted on our website.Changing Your Non-Public Personal InformationAble Label provides you with the opportunity to change your non-public personal information online for all registration information. Please contact Able Label to change any non-public personal information provided to us through a contact form. If you have any questions or concerns about any privacy issues, please contact us.
Home
About Us
Contact Us
Request Quote
Shipping
Thermal Transfer
Paper Labels
White
©  Able Label. All rights reserved.
Able Label does not claim any ownership,
sponsorship, affiliation, endorsement,
or connection with any of the other companies,
products, names or trademarks listed.
